A Guide to the Office of the Messrs. Rockefeller records, Economic Reform Interests, Series F FA315
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Chamber of Commerce - Chamber of Commerce of the State of New York - John D. Rockefeller, Jr. Mortgage Fund - Letters of Appeal, 1945-1946 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  John D. Rockefeller, Jr. served on fund raising committee.
- Chamber of Commerce - Chamber of Commerce of the State of New York - John D. Rockefeller, Jr. Election as Vice-President and Member, 1900-1955 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  Election as member, 1900; vice president, 1919.
- Chamber of Commerce - Chamber of Commerce of the State of New York - Committee on Corporate Membership, 1942-1944 (Box 7, Folder 43)
- Chamber of Commerce - Chamber of Commerce of the State of New York - Contributions, 1926-1939 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  Small gifts for special purposes.
- Chamber of Commerce - Chamber of Commerce of the State of New York - Laurance Rockefeller Membership and Interest, 1936-1958 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  Nomination by John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
- Chamber of Commerce - Chamber of Commerce of the State of New York - Committee on Commercial Arbitration, 1920-1938 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s contributions to arbitration work of Chamber.
- Chamber of Commerce - Chamber of Commerce of the State of New York - Nelson Rockefeller and John D. Rockefeller 3rd, 1935-1961 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  John D. Rockefeller 3rd and Nelson A. Rockefeller joined at the same time. Their Chamber activities, speeches, contributions. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller 3rd, Nelson A. Rockefeller.
- Chamber of Commerce - Chamber of Commerce of the State of New York - Nelson Rockefeller and John D. Rockefeller 3rd - Nelson A. Rockefeller Addresses, January 1941 (Box 7, Folder 48)
- Chamber of Commerce - Chamber of Commerce of the State of New York - Nelson Rockefeller and John D. Rockefeller 3rd - Contributions, 1936-1944 (Box 7, Folder 49)
- Chamber of Commerce - Tarrytown Chamber of Commerce, 1930-1961 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  Discussion of consolidation of Tarrytown and North Tarrytown. John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s support, contributions toward cost of surveys. Defeated. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., John D. Rockefeller 3rd, H. G. Rowell.
  56T
- Chamber of Commerce - Tarrytown Chamber of Commerce, 1938-1942 (Box 8, Folder 51)
- Chamber of Commerce - Tarrytown Chamber of Commerce - Membership Dues and Contributions, 1927-1959 (Box 8, Folder 52)
- Chamber of Commerce - Tarrytown Chamber of Commerce - Membership Dues and Contributions, 1927-1959 (Box 8, Folder 53)
- Chamber of Commerce - Tarrytown Chamber of Commerce - Dinner, April 1938 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  In honor of John D. Rockefeller, Jr. and his sons. He made a formal address. Copy here.
- Chamber of Commerce - Tarrytown Chamber of Commerce - Consolidation, 1932 (Box 8, Folder 55)
  Effort to consolidate two Tarrytowns.
- Chamber of Commerce - Tarrytown Chamber of Commerce - Consolidation, 1930 (Box 8, Folder 56)
- Chamber of Commerce - Tarrytown Chamber of Commerce - John D. Rockefeller 3rd's Addresses at Annual Dinner, October 1952 (Box 8, Folder 57)
  Tribute to S. J. Balassi by John D. Rockefeller 3rd.
- Chamber of Commerce - United States Junior Chamber of Commerce, 1933-1960 (Box 8, Folder 58)
  Invitations to join, all declined. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., John D. Rockefeller 3rd, Laurance S. Rockefeller.
  56U
- Chamber of Commerce - Westchester County Chamber of Commerce, 1921-1933 (Box 8, Folder 59)
  John D. Rockefeller, Jr. a member. Gave luncheon address in 1922. Contributions to support Public Safety program.
  56W
- National Child Labor Committee - General, 1906-1952 (Box 9, Folder 60)
  Rockefeller contributions to Committee's work; John D. Rockefeller transfers donation function to John D. Rockefeller, Jr. in 1922. Discontinued assistance; John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s gifts, 1923-1926. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
  53
- National Child Labor Committee - General, 1906-1952 (Box 9, Folder 61)
- National Child Labor Committee - Child Labor - New York Committee, 1903-1940 (Box 9, Folder 62)
  Rockefeller contributions. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Starr J. Murphy, Willard S. Richardson, Arthur W. Packard.
  53.1
- National Child Labor Committee - Child Labor - New York Committee, 1903-1940 (Box 9, Folder 63)
- Commerce and Industry Association of New York, Inc., 1949-1953 (Box 9, Folder 64)
  Formerly Merchants Association of New York. Association's activities; John D. Rockefeller, Jr. membership, contributions. Correspondents include Nelson A. Rockefeller, Laurance S. Rockefeller, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Dana S. Creel.
  100
- Commerce and Industry Association of New York, Inc., 1935-1949 (Box 9, Folder 65)
- Commerce and Industry Association of New York, Inc., 1900-1935 (Box 9, Folder 66)
- Commerce and Industry Association of New York, Inc., 1900-1961 (Box 10, Folder 67)
- Consumers Leagues - National Consumers League, 1920-1953 (Box 10, Folder 68)
  League interested in wages and hours; nominal Rockefeller support. David Rockefeller refuses to serve on various committees. Correspondents include Raymond B. Fosdick, Thomas B Appleget, Arthur W. Packard, David Rockefeller.
  94
- Consumers Leagues - National Consumers League, 1920-1953 (Box 10, Folder 69)
- Consumers Leagues - National Consumers League - Contributions, 1920-1953 (Box 10, Folder 70)
- Consumers Leagues - Consumers League of New York State, 1921-1942 (Box 10, Folder 71)
  Routine gifts by Advisory Board: no Rockefeller office initiative. Interest declined after 1938.
  94.1
- Consumers Leagues - Consumers League of New York State, 1921-1942 (Box 10, Folder 72)
- Eight Hour Day In Industry - John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s Statement, 1928-1929 (Box 10, Folder 73)
  Considerations concerning labor standards. Clippings on John D. Rockefeller, Jr.; Stewart situation. John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s anger with Providence newspaper coverage. Correspondents include Robert W. Gumbel, Thomas B. Appleget, John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
  195
- Employment Agencies - National Employment Exchange, 1909-1931 (Box 10, Folder 74)
  Private philanthropic employment agency; Rockefellers contributed some funds.
  147.1
- Employment Agencies - New York Household Placement Association, 1939-1947 (Box 10, Folder 75)
  Association of Domestic Employment agencies in New York, to protect employer and employee from unfair practices. Small contributions to aid in keeping employment agencies from state control; also in some anti-union activity. This is a very thin file. Correspondents include Thomas M. Debevoise, Arthur W. Packard.
- Employment Agencies - Executive Service Corporation, 1920-1938 (Box 10, Folder 76)
  John D. Rockefeller, Jr. (primarily on Willard S. Richardson initiative) assists financing of employment agency run by member of Riverside Bible Class. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Willard S. Richardson, A. L. Chipman.
  147.2
- Employment Agencies - Mrs. Bidwell Brown Vocational and Placement Center, Inc., 1923-1944 (Box 11, Folder 77)
  The Center was created to help find jobs and employment for gentlewomen in desperate straits. John D. Rockefeller, Jr. made one contribution, 1923. Correspondents include Willard S. Richardson, Arthur W. Packard.
  147.4
- Employment Agencies - Bureau of Part-Time Work, 1922 (Box 11, Folder 78)
  Bureau to find jobs for women who desired only part-time employment. Run on cost basis; needed assistance. John D. Rockefeller made several contributions. Correspondents include Willard S. Richardson, Arthur W. Packard, Eleanor Adler.
  147.5
- Farmer's Federation - General, 1926-1956 (Box 11, Folder 79)
  To improve farm conditions in Appalachian Highlands. Contributions by several members of the family. Inaugurated "The Lord's Acre" program for support of rural churches. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Laurance S. Rockefeller, Nelson A. Rockefeller, John D. Rockefeller 3rd, Dana S. Creel, Cyrus McCormick.
  96
- Farmer's Federation - General, 1926-1956 (Box 11, Folder 0079A)
  Correspondents include David Rockefeller.
- Farmer's Federation - John D. Rockefeller 3rd Correspondence, 1933-1956 (Box 11, Folder 80)
  John D. Rockefeller 3rd made occasional $1,000 gifts.
- Farmer's Federation - Contributions, 1953-1963 (Box 11, Folder 81)
  By Nelson A. Rockefeller, David Rockefeller, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., John D. Rockefeller 3rd, Laurance S. Rockefeller.
- Farmer's Federation - Contributions, 1936-1952 (Box 11, Folder 82)
  By Nelson A. Rockefeller, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., John D. Rockefeller 3rd, Laurance S. Rockefeller.
- Farmer's Federation - Contributions, 1936-1952 (Box 11, Folder 0082A)
  By David Rockefeller.
- Farmer's Federation - James G. K. McClure Educational and Development Fund, Inc., 1959-1961 (Box 11, Folder 83)
  Medical program for mountain folk, college scholarships, "Lord's Acre" Program. Correspondents include David Rockefeller, Dana S. Creel.
- Fifth Avenue Association - General, 1913-1961 (Box 11, Folder 84)
  John D. Rockefeller, Jr. a member. Association's programs for bettering Fifth Avenue. Rockefeller Center interest in Association. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
  164
- Fifth Avenue Association - Contributions, 1905-1961 (Box 11, Folder 85)
  By John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
- Fifth Avenue Association - Contributions, 1905-1961 (Box 11, Folder 86)
- Industrial Questions - General Correspondence (A-G), 1919-1924 (Box 12, Folder 87)
  Letters to John D. Rockefeller, Jr. suggesting programs of industrial relations; resulting from Washington Industrial Conferences and some of John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s public stands on industrial questions. Correspondents include John Spargo.
  227
- Industrial Questions - General Correspondence (H-L), 1919-1924 (Box 12, Folder 88)
- Industrial Questions - General Correspondence (M-S), 1919-1924 (Box 12, Folder 89)
- Industrial Questions - Nationalization of Coal Lands - Sankey Report, 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 90)
  Nationalization of Great Britain's coal lands; reports of English commissions to crown. John D. Rockefeller, Jr. writes to Col. R. W. Stewart suggesting that such an action in United States can be prevented by cooperating with the laboring class, keeping radicals from gaining followers. Discussion of the role of labor leaders by Harold F. McCormick and John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
  227A
- Industrial Questions - Rockefeller's Bill of Rights, 1922-1923 (Box 12, Folder 91)
  Publication of John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s Industrial Creed by R. W. Babson.
  227B
- Industrial Questions - Industrial and Labor Questions, 1937 (Box 12, Folder 92)
  Materials on unions, right to work laws, labor movement, labor legislation. Nothing directly related to Rockefeller family. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., W. W. Aldrich, John Spargo.
- Industrial Questions - American Management Association, 1922-1958 (Box 12, Folder 93)
  John D. Rockefeller, Jr. contributes to National Personnel Association. Regular contributions to budget of American Management Association. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
  227Am1
- Industrial Questions - American Council on Education, 1945-1949 (Box 12, Folder 94)
  Work on adult education, specifically job specifications and training. John D. Rockefeller, Jr. gave $12,500 in 1926-1930.
  227Am2
- Industrial Questions - American Labor Conference on International Affairs, 1945-1949 (Box 12, Folder 95)
  Rockefeller offices decline any interest in supporting Labor Conference called to support Bretton Woods agreement. Correspondents include Arthur W. Packard.
- Industrial Questions - Bureau of Personnel Administration, 1921-1938 (Box 12, Folder 96)
  John D. Rockefeller, Jr. contribution toward special study by Bureau. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Raymond B. Fosdick.
  227Ba
- Industrial Questions - Samuel Gompers and the American Federation of Labor, 1919-1943 (Box 13, Folder 97)
  Printed exchange of letters between Gompers and Newton D. Baker, re "open shop". Publication of Gompers' Memoirs, request to John D. Rockefeller, Jr. for aid from Mrs. Gompers. Nothing here on relations between Gompers and John D. Rockefeller. Correspondents include Mrs. S. Gompers, John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
  227G
- Industrial Questions - International Labor Review, 1921 (Box 13, Folder 98)
  John D. Rockefeller, Jr. writes article for Review, "Cooperation in Industry," a revised version of his Atlantic City Address, "Representation in Industry." Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., W. L. McKenzie King.
  227I
- Industrial Questions - International Labor Review, 1921 (Box 13, Folder 99)
- Industrial Questions - International Management Institute, 1927-1930 (Box 13, Folder 100)
  John D. Rockefeller, Jr. contribution to Geneva institute to promote scientific business management in Europe. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Raymond B. Fosdick.
  227I3
- Industrial Questions - International Labor Organization, 1933-1960 (Box 13, Folder 101)
  Description of International Labor Organization (ILO). Personal friendship of John D. Rockefeller 3rd with member of ILO staff. Appeal for aid in 1960 declined.
- Industrial Questions - Loyal Legion of Loggers and Lumberman, 1919-1921 (Box 13, Folder 102)
  Organization designed to counteract Industrial Workers of the World (IWW); brought to John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s attention. No active Rockefeller interest in organization.
  227L
- Industrial Questions - National Industrial Conference Board, 1917-1956 (Box 13, Folder 103)
  Organization of manufacturers and employers to offset labor pressures in American economy. John D. Rockefeller, Jr. declined to contribute or participate in organization. John D. Rockefeller 3rd attended some conferences. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Starr J. Murphy, Raymond B. Fosdick, John D. Rockefeller 3rd.
  227N1
- Industrial Questions - National Industrial Conference Board, 1917-1956 (Box 13, Folder 104)
- Industrial Questions - Data for John D. Rockefeller, Jr., 1914-1920 (Box 14, Folder 105)
  Clippings and excerpts from letters dealing with unions; held as a possible source material for speech by John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
  227Y
- Industrial Questions - President's Mediation Commission, 1918 (Box 14, Folder 106)
  Official study of labor unrest throughout country by special commission appointed by Wilson. John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s comments on real basis for industrial peace, possible forms for labor representation. Correspondents include Verner Reed, John D. Rockefeller., Jr.
- Industrial Questions - Professor J. J. Stevenson, 1914 (Box 14, Folder 107)
  John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s interest in article on "Labor and Capital." Decision to reprint and distribute it. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., J. J. Stevenson.
- Industrial Questions - Labor Unions, 1918-1920 (Box 14, Folder 108)
  Clippings, excerpts and memoranda regarding labor unions.
- Industrial Questions - Miscellaneous Articles, 1919-1921 (Box 14, Folder 109)
  Clippings, speeches, excerpts and memoranda on capital and labor, labor unrest. Accumulated in file because of John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s interest in them. Nothing significant here.
  227Z
- Industrial Questions - Miscellaneous Articles, 1921-1927 (Box 14, Folder 110)
- Industrial Questions - Washington, D. C. Industrial Conference, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 111)
  Comments by John D. Rockefeller, Jr. at conference on private property, wages, cost of living; report of Public Group to President; printed copies (9) of John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s statements at Conference. 3 copies of John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s "A New Creed for all Industry." Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
  227.1
- Industrial Questions - Washington, D. C. Industrial Conference - Report, 1919; 2 copies (Box 14, Folder 112)
- Industrial Questions - Washington, D. C. Industrial Conference - Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 113)
  Letters to John D. Rockefeller, Jr. as a result of his effort in the First Industrial Conference (1919); they express reactions to his stand there and other supplementary comments. Some of John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s responses expand on his own thoughts on capital and labor. Correspondents include W. J. Bryan, C. W. Eliott, J. J. Raskob.
- Industrial Questions - Washington, D. C. Industrial Conference - Correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 114)
  227.2
- Industrial Questions - Washington, D. C. Industrial Conference - Notes, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 115)
  Resolutions, addresses, agenda, minutes of conference; some of John D. Rockefeller, Jr.; and others not in any organized pattern. Two copies of final report. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
  227.4
- Industrial Questions - Washington, D. C. Industrial Conference - Newspaper Notices, 1919 (Box 15, Folder 116)
  On activities of Conference and John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s position in it; also on unionization, strikes, unrest.
  227.6
- Industrial Questions - Washington, D. C. Industrial Conference - Newspaper Notices, 1919 (Box 15, Folder 117)
- Industrial Questions - Washington, D. C. Industrial Conference - Industrial Disorders, 1919 (Box 15, Folder 118)
  227.7
- Industrial Questions - 2nd Industrial Conference, Washington, D. C., 1919-1920 (Box 15, Folder 119)
  Organized after failure of first conference to reach any conclusions. Unhampered by separate representation by economic groups, it drew up a report on rights of capital and labor. John D. Rockefeller, Jr. not a member.
  227.8
- Industrial Questions - Canada - National Industrial Conference, 1919-1921 (Box 15, Folder 120)
  Reports of Canadian Conference sent to John D. Rockefeller, Jr. by L. H. MacKenzie King. Frequent references to Rockefeller Plan during discussions at Conference.
  227.9
- Industrial Questions - Canada - National Industrial Conference, 1919-1921 (Box 15, Folder 121)
- Industrial Questions - Sherman Rogers, 1920-1931 (Box 15, Folder 122)
  John D. Rockefeller, Jr. supports stump speaker and writer advocating shop representation. Rogers a former logger from the Northwest; disappears from files after unsatisfactory loan experience which John D. Rockefeller, Jr. shared with six other New York businessmen. Details on loan and gifts included. Correspondents include C. A. Coffin, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Sherman Rogers.
  227.10
- Industrial Questions - Sherman Rogers - Gifts and Loans, 1920-1936 (Box 15, Folder 123)
- A. H. Lichty - Reports on Companies, 1919-1926 (Box 15, Folder 124)
  Hired by John D. Rockefeller, Jr. to survey industrial relations departments in several companies. Later hired by Colorado Fuel & Iron as Vice President in charge of Industrial Relations. Improved conditions at Colorado Fuel & Iron, 1920-1925. Fired by J. F. Welborn, 1926. Correspondents include A. H. Lichty, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., J. F. Welborn.
  228
- A. H. Lichty - Reports on Companies, 1919-1926 (Box 15, Folder 125)
- A. H. Lichty - Reports on Companies, 1919-1926 (Box 15, Folder 126)
- Industrial Relations Counselors, 1926-1958 (Box 16, Folder 127)
  Creation by Raymond B. Fosdick from earlier Rockefeller sponsored studies of Industrial Relations. Relations with Rockefeller office; research; John D. Rockefeller, Jr. contributions until 1932. Search for clients; investments; personnel questions in organizations. John D. Rockefeller 3rd served as Trustee; Winthrop Rockefeller a trustee; shift to profit making basis. Requests for research aid declined in 1958. Correspondents include Raymond B. Fosdick, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., John D. Rockefeller 3rd, Arthur w. Packard, Winthrop Rockefeller, officers of Industrial Relations Counselors (IRC).
  229
- Industrial Relations Counselors, 1926-1958 (Box 16, Folder 128)
- Industrial Relations Counselors, 1926-1958 (Box 16, Folder 129)
- Industrial Relations Counselors, 1926-1958 (Box 16, Folder 130)
- Industrial Relations Counselors, 1926-1958 (Box 16, Folder 131)
- Industrial Relations Counselors - Pledges, 1926-1958 (Box 16, Folder 132)
  John D. Rockefeller, Jr. contributions to Industrial Relations Counselors (IRC).
- Industrial Relations Counselors - Trustees, 1935-1947 (Box 16, Folder 133)
  John D. Rockefeller 3rd's role in securing Trustees; his resignation in 1947.
- Industrial Relations Counselors - C. J. Hicks, 1921-1947 (Box 16, Folder 134)
  Personal tributes to Hicks by John D. Rockefeller, Jr. Service to Industrial Relations Counselors (IRC). Memorial fellowships after death.
- Industrial Relations Counselors - C. J. Hicks, 1921-1947 (Box 16, Folder 135)
- Industrial Relations Counselors - Retirement Study, 1957-1961 (Box 17, Folder 136)
  Study on the retirement of executives, by Industrial Relations Counselors (IRC), partially financed by Rodman C. Rockefeller. No copy of report in file. Correspondents include Rodman C. Rockefeller, Dana S. Creel, James W. Tower.
- Industrial Relations Counselors - Retirement Study, 1957-1961 (Box 17, Folder 137)
- Industrial Relations Counselors - Campaigns, 1934-1936 (Box 17, Folder 138)
  John D. Rockefeller 3rd wrote appeal letters to leaders in oil industry and Carnegie Foundation raising money for budget of Industrial Relations Counselors (IRC). Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller 3rd.
  229.2
- Industrial Relations Counselors - Campaigns, 1934-1936 (Box 17, Folder 139)
- Inflation, 1935-1951 (Box 17, Folder 140)
  Pamphlets on inflation. Unsolicited suggestions for fighting inflation sent to Rockefeller office; studies of effects of inflation in Europe, 1920-1923.
  184
- Inflation, 1935-1951 (Box 17, Folder 141)
- National Organizations of Economic Research - National Bureau of Economic Research, 1912-1961 (Box 18, Folder 142)
  To collect and disseminate facts about business. Designed to offset unfavorable publicity caused by the muckrakers. Planned by J. P. Morgan, Thomas Vail, N. W. Aldrich. John D. Rockefeller, Jr. interested but wary; Rockefeller group emphasizes research. Pungent letters by Frederick T. Gates prevented Rockefeller Foundation support. A second organization of same name set up in 1920. John D. Rockefeller, Jr. contributions. Correspondents include Starr J. Murphy, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Raymond B. Fosdick, E. F. Gay.
  95
- National Organizations of Economic Research - National Bureau of Economic Research, 1912-1961 (Box 18, Folder 0142A)
  David Rockefeller became a subscriber in 1942. Correspondents include David Rockefeller.
- National Organizations of Economic Research - National Bureau of Economic Research, 1912-1961 (Box 18, Folder 143)
- National Organizations of Economic Research - National Economic League, 1918-1938 (Box 18, Folder 144)
  Tried to interest John D. Rockefeller, Jr. in program of economic conservation. No success. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
  95.1
- National Organizations of Economic Research - Economists National Committee on Monetary Policy, 1935-1958 (Box 18, Folder 145)
  Organized to fight inflation; primarily a propaganda effort rather than educational. No family interest. Correspondents include Arthur W. Packard, Dana S. Creel.
  95.2
- National Organizations of Economic Research - The Twentieth Century Fund, 1946-1961 (Box 18, Folder 146)
  Information on fund's activities. No Rockefeller participation in its work. Correspondents include Arthur W. Packard.
  95.4
- New York City Building Zone Law, 1916-1942 (Box 18, Folder 147)
  Zoning Committee (an independent organization) requests aid from John D. Rockefeller, Jr. His interest stemmed from his large real estate holdings in New York City and his desire to keep the city livable; made yearly contributions, 1917-1942, ranging from $100 to $1,000. Correspondents include F. B. Pratt, Edward Bassett, Charles O. Heydt, John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
  112